你又回来干什么
What are you doing back?
我不想再重复这事了
We can't go over this again.
回家吧  睡个好觉
Go home. Get some sleep.
看着自己的妈这样忘记情伤可真诡异的
It is so weird watching your mother try to rebound.
她肯用心打扮一下是个好兆头
Well, taking care of her appearance is a good sign, actually.
她在跟一切会走的东西调情
She's flirting with everything that moves.
她有没有说她和卡瓦诺夫分手的原因
Did she tell you why Cavanaugh broke it off?
没有
No.
我倒希望她能说出来
I wish she'd talk about it.
你知道女人一生中平均要摄入
Do you know the average woman ingests 7 pounds of lipstick
七磅唇膏吗
over a lifetime?
你为什么坚持不懈地在食物面前
Why do you insist on telling me
跟我分享倒胃口的有趣事实
your disgusting fun facts over food?
那是咖啡
It's coffee.
-你好啊美女  -你好
- Hiya, doll! - Hi!
警探好
Detective.
这么多傻瓜可供她选择
Of all the knuckleheads she's gonna flirt with --
她就非得跟闪电麦坤调情吗[汽车总动员2的角色]
She has to flirt with Lightning McQueen?
我以为他叫吉布森警探
I thought his name was detective Gibson.
他隶属偷车特别小组
I believe he's part of the auto-theft task force.
这可以解释为什么他这么自大
That explains why he's so arrogant.
看好了
Watch this. Watch.
如果用车来形容你
If you were a car,
我会说是68年产的道奇战马
you'd be a '68 Dodge charger --
外观时髦  路跑的性能好
Sleek styling, great street performance.
警探你好
Hey, detective.
我在跟你妈妈聊着
I was, uh, I was just telling your mother
我们找到的68年产的道奇战马
about this, uh, '68 dodge charger we recovered.
真的吗
Really?
我以为你要称赞她的好身材呢
I thought you were about to compliment her on her trunk space.
简
Jane!
早上好  警督
Good morning, lieutenant.
有什么好的
What's good about it?
所以  高帅富你照惯例下单吗
So...rich, I guess you'll have your usual.
安琪拉  你怎么这么了解我呢
Angela, how can you know me so well?
现在她是在想让卡瓦诺夫吃醋吗
Now she's trying to make Cavanaugh jealous?
吃醋有时候是爱或者承诺的表现
Jealousy can sometimes be a sign of love or commitment.
也可能是闪电麦坤将要遭殃
It can also be a sign that Lightning McQueen
的一个信号
is about to get his ass kicked.
晚点见  美女
So, I'll be seeing you, beautiful.
好的  再见
Okay. Bye, rich.
-我打电话给你  -好的
- I will call you. - Okay.
里佐利夫人  如果你有空
Hey, Mrs. Rizzoli, if you're not too busy,
可不可以来这里加点咖啡
can I get some coffee over here?
马上来  警督
Right away, lieutenant.
我看不下去了
I can't watch any more.
我们不能袖手旁观
We have to do something.
要怎么做  把塑料刀都藏起来吗
What? Hide all the plastic knives?
小香草
Vanilla.
就在找你呢
Just who I was looking for.
我以为你想喝咖啡
I thought you wanted some coffee.
不用了
Uh, never mind.
你好  朗多先生  这是什么情况
Hello, Mr. Rondo. Who do we have here?
他们是罗本  丹尼亚  特雷弗
Reuben, Dania, Trevor.
我叫道格[狗]
It's Dawg.
你好吗  道格
How do you do, Dawg?
朗多  我们已经过了参加儿童聚会的年龄了
Rondo, aren't we a little old for playdates?
他们是我在"街边"的朋友
These are all my homies from "Off the street."
青少年寄宿处?
The home for teenagers?
我在那里当志愿者
I volunteer there.
我们是"朗多的次品"
We're "Rondo's rejects."
也许你们可以换个没这么贬义的名字
Perhaps you'd consider a less pejorative name.
青少年通常认同于社会对他们的定位
Juveniles often identify with the labels society gives them.
社会没给他们定位  名字是他们自己取的
Oh, society didn't name them. They named their own selves.
次品是指达不到
Um, a reject is a person or thing
-正常标准的人或物  -莫拉
- dismissed as failing to meet standards -- - Maura.
"贬义"是表示
"Pejorative" is a word
蔑视或者谴责的词语
that expresses contempt or disapproval.
我带他们来是见英雄的
Brought 'em by to meet my heroes --
"职业日"的即兴活动
a little impromptu "Career Day."
所以你们想当警察吗
Wow. So you guys want to be cops?
才不要
No. No way.
他们只是要些指导
They just need a little mentoring.
你可不可以带他们逛一下
Maybe you could... take 'em around a little?
我也可以当导师  有谁喜欢烹饪吗
I-I could be a mentor, too. Does anybody like cooking?
烹饪
Cooking!
-或者科学  -科学
- Or science? - Science!
好了  妈  给他们准备甜甜圈
Okay, ma, why don't you give them a doughnut,
然后你们喜欢什么就什么吧
and we'll let you be on your way?
我同意
Fine by me.
就是  反正我是不会跟女人学习的
Right? I ain't being mentored by no chick, anyway.
现在我想了一下
You know, now that I think about it,
我们喜欢当导师
we love to mentor here.
如果你们喜欢的话  可以找个男警探
And we can find a boy detective, if that's what you'd prefer.
弗罗斯特警探当你的导师
Detective Frost could be your mentor.
科萨克警司可以当你的导师
And Sergeant Korsak could be your mentor.
如果非得给我找导师
If I have to have a mentor,
我希望他有高级学位
I'd rather it be someone with an advanced degree.
我有医学博士学位
I have an M.D.
行
Okay, I guess.
有东西吃吗
You got anything to eat?
妈  我们得走了  有案件
Okay, ma, we got to go. We got a case.
进来吧  我给你们做早饭
All right, come on. I'll make you all breakfast.
弗兰基
Frankie!
过来
Come here!
我要你帮我做点事
I need you to do something.
有大案件吗
You got a big case?
你看见那边的几个小孩没
You see those teenagers over there?
查一下名字  确保他们没杀过人
Run their names -- make sure they haven't killed anybody.
你是指围着妈的那个人吗
You mean the ones standing 6 inches from ma?
或许你应该别让他们走出你视线范围
You probably shouldn't let them out of your sight, either.
如果天行者没有尤达大师会怎么办[星球大战人物]
Where would Luke Skywalker be without Yoda?
或者是龙威小子没有宫城师父
Or the Karate Kid without Mr. Miyagi?
好了  我都答应去当导师了
Okay, I said I would do it. I'll be a mentor.
阿格娜蒂斯是古雅典的第一位
Agnodice was the first female gynecologist
女性妇产医生
in ancient Athens.
她曾经当过我的导师
She was one of my mentors.
你在说你穿越时空回到一世纪吗
You mean when you time-traveled back to the 1st century?
是公元前三世纪
3rd century B.C.
居里夫人也对我影响深远
Marie Curie was also a big influencer of mine.
你的导师有谁
Who were your mentors?
《女警》  《侦探科杰克》[70年代的电影]
Uh, Police Woman, Kojak...
还有吉姆・罗克福德[《罗克福德档案》的主角]
Oh! Jim Rockford.
他在煮什么
What was he cooking?
-啤酒  -啤酒
- Beer. - Beer?
他是制作微酿啤酒的  这是他的实验厨房
He's a microbrewer. This is his test kitchen.
死者是格雷格・扬森
Victim is Greg Jensen,
霸王啤酒的总裁和酿酒师
C.E.O. and brewmaster of Overlord Ale.
谁发现尸体的
Who found the body?
扬森的助手  罗比・伯克
Jensen's assistant, Ruby Burke.
今早发现的
She found him this morning.
然后我回来  就
And then I came back, and...
她有不在场证据吗
She have an alibi?
她过去的一个月在斯堪的纳维亚半岛[北欧]
Yeah, she was in Scandinavia for the last month.
她在卖以北欧维京海盗为主题的啤酒
She was selling her boss's viking-themed beer.
今早刚从雷克雅维克飞回来[冰岛首都]
She flew in from Reykjavik this morning.
遇害时间是几点
When was he killed?
他至少死了八小时
He's been dead at least eight hours.
-海报女郎真惹火  -确实
- Sweet poster girl. - No kidding.
先生们
Uh, gentlemen?
有没有嫌疑人
Do we have any suspects?
死者已婚  已经通知了他的妻子
Oh, victim's married. Wife's been notified.
据称她当时在家照看两个小孩
Says she was home taking care of their two young kids.
我们会带她过来
We're bringing her in.
2.5公分的圆孔
2.5-centimeter round hole.
这可真是个不一般的伤口啊
That's a very unusual entrance wound.
他是被什么刺伤的
What was he stabbed with?
不是刀
Not a knife.
我们又是在玩排除法吗
Are we playing "Process of elimination" again?
答对了
Yes.
凶器不是垃圾处理器
It's not a garbage disposal,
不是劈刀  不是干草叉
Cleaver, pitchfork,
不是锯齿剪切机
pinking shears...
女士们
Uh, ladies?
好的
Right.
但这个东西看起来像是个铆钉
But this...appears to be a metal rivet.
可能是从作案工具上掉下来的
Maybe it came off the murder weapon.
发现了些血滴
There's some blood droplets...
一直滴到了碾磨器这里
...leading into that mill.
我觉得我们找到了作案凶器
I think we just found what's left of our murder weapon.
血迹确认了棍子上的血是扬森的
The trace confirmed that the blood on the stick belonged to Jensen.
你觉得一根削尖的棍子能造成这样的伤害吗
You think a sharpened stick could do that kind of damage?
是的
Yeah.
尽管还无法解释铆钉是怎么来的
Doesn't explain the metal rivet, though.
嘿  简
Hey. Jane.
天哪  弗兰基  对不起
Oh, my g-- Frankie, I'm so sorry.
没关系
Oh, no problem.
我一直在和你的徒弟们有说有笑呢
I've been having a barrel of laughs with your mentees.
谁收了徒弟吗
Who has mentees?
额  是你
Um...you.
还有你
And you.
显然莫拉和简把我们都变成了志愿者
Apparently, Maura and Jane volunteered all of us --
带他们参观了嫌犯登记  一些用品
Toured booking, properties.
我刚还想向他们展示如何写交通罚单的呢
I was just about to show them how I write a traffic ticket.
你一直在打呼噜
This is snore-ville -- population, you.
他们现在归你们了
They're all yours.
你好
Hey. Hello.
嗨
Hi!
请别玩这个
Please... don't play with that.
为什么你有个玩偶
Why you got a doll, man?
我想我能否去看下法医
I was wondering if I could go see the medical examiner,
兴许能看看尸检过程
Maybe check out an autopsy?
不行
Uh...no.
为什么不行
Why not?
因为这个不在日程安排上
'cause it's not on the itinerary.
我正在学高阶生物学
I'm taking A.P. Bio, so --
-高阶生物学吗  -没错
- Advanced-placement biology? - Yeah
怎么  你觉得次品少年就不配聪明吗
What, you think a reject kid can't be smart?
至少次品少年不玩玩偶
At least reject kids don't play with dolls.
我赌你管这个玩偶叫仿真玩具人
Wait. I bet you call him an action figure,
对吗  兄弟
right, bro?
没错  如果你敢再动它一下
Yes, and if you touch my "Action figure" Again,
我就打烂你的脸
I will break your face.
如果我能观摩一场尸检的话
If I could observe an autopsy,
就可以给我加额外学分了
it'd count for extra credit.
好吧
Okay, fine.
但你得让你的父母签
But you need to have your parents sign
这个豁免责任书
this liability release waiver.
不是这样的  丹尼亚  是你的父母
No, Dania, your parents got to --
这是合法的  我有自主权
It's legal. I'm emancipated.
我的妈妈死了  我的爸爸在监狱里
My mom's dead, and my dad's in prison.
如果你不信的话  这是我的资料
If you don't believe me, here are my documents.
好吧  跟我来
Okay. Come on.
等等  我们也想看看尸体
W-w-w-w-wait. We want to see dead bodies, too.
没错  总比在这胡扯要好
Yeah. Better than this bullshit.
哦  真可惜
Oh, shoot.
我赌现在你们真希望选的是女警探
I bet you wish you picked the "Chick" Detective now.
对不住了  小伙子们
Sorry, fellas.
把他盖起来
Cover him up.
盖起来  莫拉  盖起来
Cover him up, Maura. Cover him up.
你好
Hi.
你是要切Y形切口吗
You're about to do the "Y" Incision?
是的
Yes!
你知道为什么要切Y形吗  丹尼亚
And do you know why the "Y," Dania?
是为了更好的移动胸甲部位
To facilitate the removal of the breastplate.
快切吧
Go ahead. Do it.
不行
Uh...no.
豁免责任书里并未涵盖解剖尸体
Our release form doesn't cover slicing and dicing.
你说过我能观摩尸检的
You said I could check out an autopsy.
我没说是哪个部分
I didn't say which part.
好吧  我们要做的第一件事
Okay, so, the first thing that I do
就是检查尸体
is examine the body.
你的责任书里包括手套了吗
Does your release form cover gloves?
是的
Yes.
好了  你注意到什么了吗
All right. Do you notice anything?
他的小腿有些浮肿  但我看不到外伤
His leg's a little swollen, but I don't see an injury.
你很有洞察力
You're very observant.
你觉得这可能会是深静脉血栓造成的吗
You think it could be deep-vein thrombosis?
我是从一名战地记者的资料里读到的
I read about this war correspondent
他是因为在一个地方坐的太久而造成了死亡
who died from sitting in one place for too long.
莫拉  小心咯
Better be careful, Maura.
我觉得我发现了你的接替者了
I think we found your replacement.
我能看看伤口吗
Can I see the wound?
这是什么凶器造成的
What kind of weapon did that?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
但这种锯齿状的伤口边缘表明
But the ragged wound edges suggest
是某种带刺的刀刃所致
some kind of a barbed blade.
警探  你能帮我把他翻个身吗
Detective, can you help me turn him on his side?
没问题
Yeah, sure.
好的
Okay.
这就好
There we go.
我们要用莹光镜近距离看一下
We'll take a closer look with the fluoroscope.
有东西卡在t-8部位了
There's something lodged near t-8.
看起来像是某种矛尖
Looks like some kind of spear tip.
它看起来像是一种铁制的矛
It looks like an iron krokspjot.
哈  正如我猜的那样
Aha! Just as I suspected
它是个"电锅"(读错了)
-- a crockpot.
像这样的矛是在维京时期使用的
Krokspjots like this were used during the Viking era.
我觉得金属上刻的是符文
I think these are rune letters carved into the metal.
这种符文字母是一种古老的北欧字母
The runic alphabet is an ancient nordic one
早于拉丁文
that predates latin.
你能读懂它写的是什么吗
Can you read what it says?
不能  我得去咨询一下符文方面的专家
No. I'll have to consult a runic scholar.
格雷格・扬森销售的是维京主题的啤酒
Well, Greg Jensen sold Viking-themed beer.
也许矛尖是从他的酿酒厂或是咖啡中来的
Maybe the spear tip came from his brewery or his office.
弗罗斯特和科萨克找到了嫌疑犯的线索
Okay, Frost and Korsak have a lead on a possible suspect.
跟我走  丹尼亚
Come on, Dania.
酷  我能看你胁迫嫌犯吗
Cool. Can I watch you intimidate the suspect?
不行  但快跟上
No. But hurry.
我不想让你错失我妈的烹饪课
I don't want you to miss my mother's cooking class.
谢谢你妈的烹饪课
Thank your mom for that cooking class.
不然道格和罗本差不多
Dawg and Reuben almost
就要被敲脑袋了
got slapped upside the head.
科萨克  你是要打你的徒弟吗
Korsak, you were gonna hit your mentees?
不是我  是弗罗斯特
Not me -- Frost.
冷面先生不能接受青少年的态度
Mr. Chill can't take teen 'tude.
看看这个
Take a look at this.
那是霸王啤酒的标志
That is the overlord ale logo.
但看这个
But look at this.
为什么有人想要加入北欧摩托车暴力团伙
Why would a brother want to be in a nordic motorcycle gang?
世界毁灭骑手是个摩托俱乐部
Ragnarok riders is a motorcycclub.
不是暴力团伙  弗罗斯特
It's not a gang, Frost.
这个摩托俱乐部的标志
Well, the motorcycle-club logo is
和霸王啤酒的标志很像啊
similar to overlord ale.
别跟我说受害者抄袭了摩托俱乐部的标志
Don't tell me our victim lifted a motorcycle club's logo.
还有更糟的
It gets worse.
看到了那个性感的维京海报女郎了吗
See the sexy Viking poster girl?
看到了
Yes.
这位是苏菲・韦斯特
Meet Sophie West.
这是她和她父亲
Here she is with her daddy.
克拉克・韦斯特  人称"杀人王"
Clark "Skull Crusher" West --
世界毁灭骑手的老大
head of the Ragnarok Riders.
他起诉了格雷格・扬森  告他侵犯版权
He sued Greg Jensen, claiming copyright infringement.
那是  总不能告他侵犯他女儿
Yeah, 'cause he couldn't sue for daughter infringement.
扬森雇了苏菲当霸王啤酒的模特
Jensen paid Sophie to be the model for Overlord Ale.
她父亲为了商标权起诉  却输了
Daddy sued over the logo and lost.
那家伙可输不起
The guy's a sore loser.
小心着点儿  呆子
Hey, you watch yourself, pencil neck.
你给我小心
You watch your back.
这事儿没完
This battle isn't over.
看来我们得去拜访一下这位"杀人王"了
Oh, I think we should pay Skull Crusher a visit.
不是演习  今天没安排演习
That's not a drill. Nothing's scheduled today.
大伙儿快离开这儿
Get the hell out of here, people!
现在就走  快
Let's move -- now!
快走
Go!
从内罗毕带回来的那个面具我没拿
I left my mask from Nairobi inside.
我没拿我的幸运笔记本
I left my lucky notepad.
早知道拿那幅瑞士版画了
I should've grabbed my Swiss lithographs.
你看那栋楼  看到烟没有
Look at this building. Do you see any smoke?
没有
No.
那你的超灵敏鼻子闻到烟味没有
And does your super-sniffer nose smell any smoke?
没有
No.
我看是朗多带来的哪个"次品"
I think one of Rondo's rejects
拉响了火警警报
pulled the fire alarm
省得听妈那"享受新鲜果蔬"的长篇大论
to get out of ma's "fun with fresh produce" lecture.
好了  各位
All right, everybody.
有人开玩笑拉了火警警报
Some joker pulled the fire alarm.
回去工作吧
Let's get back to work.
就知道是假警报
Told you -- false alarm.
弗兰基
Frankie!
妈  怎么了
Ma. What's the matter?
我的钱包被偷了
Someone stole my wallet!
好吧  我提了工资
Okay, I cashed my paycheck.
把钱包放进包里
I put my wallet in my purse.
像往常一样把包放在了柜台下面
I keep my purse underneath the counter, like I always do.
这可不安全
That's not very safe.
那是当然  莫拉  多谢提醒
Clearly, Maura. Thank you.
你不会以为是
You don't think...
没错  我就是这么想的
Yeah.Do think.
我也是
Me too.
我要把这些面具藏好
I'm gonna go put these masks away.
对了  把它们放保险箱里
Okay, put them in the safe.
我没有保险箱
I don't have a safe.
没人要你的面具  莫拉
No one's taking your masks, Maura.
行了  你们哪个偷了钱包
Okay, which one of you snapped the wallet? Hmm?
听着  不管是谁"找到"我妈的钱包
Look, anyone of you that "found" my mother's wallet,
现在交出来的话  就不告你
you return it now, we don't press charges.
你们听到小香草警探的话了吧
You heard Detective Vanilla.
你们谁有罪
If one of you is the guilty party,
快坦白吧
guilty party better speak up.
我没偷钱包
I didn't steal no wallet.
我也没有
Me either.
我要找律师
I want a lawyer.
站起来
Stand up.
快
Do it!
把手摊开
Hold your hands out.
不管谁拉的警报  手上肯定留有隐形染料
Whoever pulled the fire alarm is gonna have U.V. dye residue.
那又怎样
So?
-我碰警报器是为了关掉它  -当然了
- I touched the alarm to turn it off. - Sure you did.
我没偷钱包  好吗
I didn't steal no wallet, all right?
你们没证据
You can't prove nothin'.
是没有  不过拉警报这事可以告你轻罪
No, but we can file a misdemeanor for pulling the alarm.
你们可能不相信  但他们都是好孩子
I-I know it don't seem like it, but they're all good kids.
道格拿到了波士顿剑桥大学的奖学金
Dawg has a scholarship to BCU,
他要是惹上麻烦奖学金就没了
and he could lose it if he gets in trouble.
什么叫"要是"
"If"?
他已经有麻烦了
Oh, he's in trouble.
你找到那钱包  朗多  我们那时再谈
You find that wallet, Rondo. Then we'll talk.
真难受
I feel bad.
你以为跟我们待上二十分钟
Well, you think 20 minutes with us
就能彻底改变他们的人生吗
is gonna turn their lives around?
你们好  你们也是来支持儿童癌症骑行的吗
Hello. Are you here to support the kids' cancer ride, too?
波士顿警局凶案组  我们要找克拉克・韦斯特
Uh, Boston Homicide. We're looking for Clark West.
克拉克
Clark!
你们想知道什么
What do you want?
我们在调查一起凶案
We're investigating a homicide.
没问你  问这位女士呢
I wasn't asking you. I was asking the lady.
鄙人克拉克・韦斯特
Clark West.
朋友都叫我"杀人王"
My friends call me "Skull Crusher."
你想坐中间吗  警探
Can you ride bitch, detective?
不行  我可不是个好乘客
No. I'm a terrible passenger.
我们是来调查一起谋杀案的
We're here about a murder.
我很忙  正筹备慈善骑行呢
I'm busy -- getting ready for a charity ride.
你看着办吧  要么回答我们的问题
Here's your choice -- you can answer our questions
要么享受一下挤在巡逻车里的滋味
or enjoy a bitch ride in a squad car
跟我们回总部
back to headquarters.
就给你们半分钟时间
You got 30 seconds of my attention.
格雷格・扬森  你起诉的那个啤酒师
Greg Jensen, the beer maker you sued,
昨天被杀了
was murdered yesterday.
那家伙是个混蛋
Well, guy's a prick.
他罪有应得
He might have had something like that coming.
我们看了你在法院威胁他的视频
We have video of you threatening Greg Jensen at the courthouse.
他盗用我俱乐部的商标
He stole my club logo,
还让我女儿给她做广告
made my daughter his marketing bitch.
你昨天在哪儿
Where were you yesterday?
昨天
Yesterday...
麻省总医院  小儿癌症中心
Mass General, pediatric cancer center,
给孩子们送玩具和书籍
bringing toys and books to the kids.
要看照片吗
You want to see the photos?
大个子卡尔把相机都拍爆了
Big Karl here maxed out the camera memory.
很可爱
Really cute.
不过挺悲伤的
It was sad, though.
祝你们骑行顺利
Good luck with your ride.
谢谢
Thank you.
我拍了矛尖上符文的照片
I e-mailed a photo of the rune letters on the spear tip
发给了以前教我北欧历史的教授
to my old nordic-history professor.
意思是"无骨奥拉夫"
It says "Olaf the boneless."
是北欧海盗汤的配方吗
It's a...recipe for viking soup?
不知道是不是想说"伊娃"
Hmm. Could they have meant "Ivar," I wonder?
原来你也这么想
Mm. You too?
曾经有过一个北欧海盗首领叫"无骨伊娃"
Well, there was a viking leader named Ivar the boneless.
有学者认为他是个残疾的侏儒
Some scholars believed that he was a disabled dwarf
被人用盾牌抬着上战场
who was carried into battle on his shield.
是个真正的勇士
He was a great warrior.
坐着盾牌的无骨侏儒怎么能是勇士呢
How is a boneless dwarf on a shield a great warrior --
亏你想得出来
How do you manage to do this?
想什么
Do what?
一个无骨的侏儒
A boneless dwarf --
你急着找我干嘛
What was so urgent?
犯罪化验室在死者的防化服里面
The crime lab found seminal fluid
发现了混有阴道分泌物的精液
mixed with vaginal secretions in the victim's tyvek suit.
应该是一个月前留下的
It appears to be a month old.
在里面吗
"In"?
你是说死者大概一个月前发生了性事
So our victim had sex about a month ago
然后还穿这件一次性的防化服
and then wore his disposable tyvek suit again?
没错
Yes.
而且枪尖上也发现有阴道分泌物
And they also found vaginal secretions on the spear.
好吧  这是史上最恶心的微物迹证了
Okay, that qualifies as the grossest trace evidence ever.
放轻松  分泌物在这里
Relax. The secretions were here.
可能是沾到了
Probably from transfer.
差不多一个月之久了
Also about a month old.
两个都有足够的微孔材料来提取DNA
And there was enough cellular material in both to extract DNA.
我们正在处理
We're running it.
所以凶手可能是个女人
So our killer could be a woman.
因为这么锋利的武器
Well, since a weapon this sharp
不需要多大力气  有可能
doesn't need much force, it's possible.
科萨克在询问受害者的妻子
Korsak is interviewing the victim's wife.
我需要一个擦拭工具
I need one of those swabby things.
住手  我来帮你拿
W-- stop! I'll get you whatever you're looking for.
可我需要更多精准的描述
But I need a more precise description.
一天到晚我得绞尽脑汁理解你说的话
I have to figure out what you say all day long.
你连"擦拭工具"都听不懂吗  是吗
You can't figure out "Swabby thing"? Really?
扬森夫人  这位是里佐利警探
Mrs. Jensen, this is detective Rizzoli.
对你丈夫的死表示遗憾
Very sorry for your loss.
谢谢
Thank you.
扬森夫人刚告诉我
Mrs. Jensen was just telling me
她丈夫曾经经常消失几天
that her husband often disappeared for days at a time.
你知道他去哪里了吗
You have any idea where he was going?
他说他在研究一种新的啤酒配方
He said he was working on a new ale recipe.
但是我很怀疑
But I had my suspicions.
我觉得他有外遇了
I think he was having an affair.
我说对了  是吗
I'm right, aren't I?
我们在你丈夫衣服上找到了一个女人的DNA
We found a woman's DNA on your husband's clothing.
大约一个月前  他有没有
Was he gone for an extended period of time
消失过一段时间
about a month ago?
这种事情持续了将近一年
This has been going on for almost a year.
你应该能理解我们需要你的DNA
You understand that we'll need to rule you out
来将你排除吧
as a source of that DNA?
当然  没问题
Yeah, of course.
尽你们所需
Whatever you guys need.
我在我丈夫车里发现了另一部手机
I found a second phone in my husband's car.
应该叫一次性手机
I believe they're called "Burn" Phones.
我记下了号码
I wrote the number down.
也许会有帮助
Maybe that'll help.
谢谢
Thank you.
弗罗斯特警探你在想什么
What were you thinking detective Frost.
我没在想什么  长官
I wasn't thinking, sir.
你肯定没有
You sure as hell weren't.
对不起  长官
I'm sorry, sir.
这是怎么回事
What was that all about?
我泡了榛子咖啡
I made hazelnut coffee.
显然  他不喜欢榛子
Apparently, he doesn't like hazelnut.
老天
Oh, boy.
卡瓦诺夫为什么心情如此不好
Why is cavanaugh in such a lousy mood?
因为他和我妈分手了
'cause he broke up with my mother.
你在开玩笑吧
You're kidding me.
你看起来不那么惊讶啊
You don't look too surprised.
你妈向我倾诉了一切
Uh... your mother confided in me,
让我什么都别说
and asked me not to say anything.
很高兴她能找你倾诉  她真的很受伤
Well, good. I'm glad she had you to talk to. She was really hurt.
我觉得她仍然喜欢他
I think she still likes him.
你怎么想的
How do you feel about that?
现在是给爱管闲事夫人树立榜样的时候了
Like it's time to set a good example for Mrs. Buttinsky
不要成为爱管闲事的警探
and not be detectibuttinsky.
查下这个号码  这是受害人的一次性手机
Run this number, will you? It's our victim's burn phone.
我觉得妻子是清白的
Wife seems clean to me.
我也觉得
Me too.
我猜格雷格不用这个手机
I'm guessing ol' Greg wasn't calling home
打给家里
on that second phone.
是这样
Yeah, he was.
不给他本来的家打
But not the family home.
我们的死者为两个地址设了不同电话
Our boy had two phones for two addresses.
他用他的秘密手机
He was using his secret batphone
打给
to call...
他一年前买的后湾公寓
a back bay condo he bought a year ago.
我觉得他不仅背着妻子偷情
I'm thinking not only was he cheating on his wife,
还有了小爱巢
he had a little love nest.
咱们去查查
Let's go toss it.
波士顿警察  开门
Boston police! Open the door!
安全
Clear.
我觉得所有的喊叫声都是游里的戏
I think all that yelling is just this game.
安全
Clear.
无骨奥拉夫
Olaf the boneless.
和扎死他的矛尖
That's the same name
上写的名字一样
that was on the spear tip that killed him.
一定是扬森的用户名
Must be Jensen's user name.
他喜欢玩游戏
Man. He liked playing.
他至今在线2738个小时
He's logged 2,738 hours.
他也有一些高级武器
He has some high-level weapons, too --
波杰尔斧  托尔锤
Porgeir's ax, thor's hammer.
和一个萨迦盾
And a saga shield?
我靠
Damn!
你懂得真多啊  弗罗斯特
You seem to know a lot about this, Frost.
我玩过多人在线网络对战游戏
I've dabbled in M.M.O.R.P.G.
你玩过
Have you?
很多人一起在线玩角色扮演游戏
Massive multiplayer online role-playing games.
这个游戏叫维京王国
This one's called "Vikings of the realm."
你为什么会浪费2700个小时玩电脑游戏
Why would you waste 2,700 hours playing a computer game?
为了荣耀
Points.
什么荣耀
Points for what?
赢
To win!
赢什么
Win what?!
好吧  那么  格雷格・扬森
Okay, so...Greg Jensen
经营一家成功的现酿啤酒厂
ran a successful microbrewing company,
但他大部分时间在扮演无骨奥拉夫
but he pretended to be "Olaf the boneless" most of the time.
看看这个
Look at this --
上个月寄到受害者信箱的信
Snail mail, addressed to the victim at a P.O. Box, sent within the last month.
没有回信地址  不认识
No return address. Can't read it.
看来像符文写的
Looks like it's written in rune.
看这个
Hey, look at this.
下一个就是你的妓女
"Your whore is next."
凶手可能还没有停手
I'm thinking our killer isn't done.
如果我们要了同一个口味
I'm just saying it's more cost-effective
那要一夸脱冻酸奶更合算
to get a quart of frozen yogurt if we're sharing the same flavors.
我喜欢我自己的
I like my own, okay?
你为什么不喜欢搅拌呢
Well, why don't you like it swirled?
还是摩卡和薄荷味
It's still mocha and mint.
不  一搅拌就成一种味道了
No. When you swirl it, it becomes one flavor.
咖啡牙膏味
Coffee toothpaste.
别把你的香肠油滴到我这半
Don't get your pepperoni grease on my half.
好吧  把你的香菇从我这半拿走
Okay, get your mushroom off my half.
你和你妈聊过吗
Did you talk to your mother?
我们离开的时候卡瓦诺夫中尉很痛苦
Lieutenant Cavanaugh looked miserable when we left.
也许是因为我们有一个凶手躲在
Well, maybe because we have an unsolved homicide
游戏里的凶杀案还没破
with a killer hiding in a video game.
是谁
Who's that?
不是吧  一个淡紫色大众汽车窃听器
He did not! A lavender vw bug?
我对天发誓  淡紫色  一个人
God's honest truth -- lavender, for a guy who's...
你能感受到我吗
You feel me?
谁要感受你  吉布森警探
Who's gonna feel you, detective Gibson?
里佐利警探
Detective Rizzoli.
你好吗
How are you?
我只是顺道送你妈
Uh...I was just dropping your mother off.
经你允许了吗
Did you permit this?
我确定当他们在你妈床上爱爱的时候
Well, I insisted they each have one foot on the floor
各有一只脚在地板上
when there's heavy petting on your mother's bed.
真好笑
You're so funny.
妈  我能跟你聊一会儿吗
Uh, ma, can I talk to you for a sec?
好...好的
Uh...s-sure.
我先上楼了
Oh, hey, I'm just gonna go upstairs.
我好像忘记给我的电动牙刷充电了
I think I forgot to charge my electric toothbrush.
好了  你为什么这么对卡瓦诺夫警督
Okay, why are you doing this to Lieutenant Cavanaugh?
简  这跟你一点关系都没有
Okay, Jane, this is so not your business.
关系大着呢
Yeah, it is.
特别是现在他把火全撒在我们身上
Especially when he's taking it out on all of us.
整个警队呢
The -- the entire squad.
那只能说明他比我想的幼稚多了
Well, then he's more juvenile than I thought he was.
你想听听什么叫幼稚
You want to hear juvenile?
"你要是辆车  肯定是辆68年的道奇战马"
"If you were a car, you'd be a '68 Dodge Charger."
你根本都不喜欢那个傻瓜
You don't even like that goofball.
别这么叫他
Don't call him that.
而且我喜欢他
And I do, too!
我才不信
I don't believe you.
如果你这么做只是为了让卡瓦诺夫吃醋
And if you are doing this just to get to Cavanaugh,
那我会告诉你你跟我说过的话
then I'm gonna say the same thing you told me.
别这样  这不合你的身份
Don't. It's beneath you.
简
Jane.
妈  你是在哭吗
Wh-- ma? A-are you crying?
我太为你骄傲了
I'm so proud of you.
你哭个什么呀
W-w-why are you crying?
因为我把你养大  你出落成漂亮的大姑娘
Because I raised you -- I raised a beautiful girl.
而且
And...
你说的对
...you're right.
谢谢
Thank you.
我爱你  妈
I love you, ma.
我也爱你
I love you more.
谢谢  美人
Thanks, gorgeous.
警探
Detective.
这是个好兆头
That's a good sign.
起码她没再让人注意她的嘴了
At least she's not drawing attention to her mouth.
没有调情的迹象
No sign of flirtation.
保时捷惨败了  我需要一杯提神酒
I needed a pick-me-up after that porsche fiasco.
你听说这事了吗  里佐利
You hear about this, Rizzoli?
大家都在说这事呢
Everybody's talking about it.
是啊  大家都在说破烂的"保时吉"  吉布森
Oh, yeah, everyone's talking about that old "Porsh," Gibson.
是"保时捷"
It's "Porsh-ah."
是吗
Really?
吉布森是意大利名吗
"Gibson" is an italian name?
不是
No.
不过咱们中有人对意大利高级车如数家珍
But some of us know a lot about high-end Italian rides.
那是德国车  你这傻子
It's a German car, you idiot.
我觉得他们俩是在拆裆
I think they're crotch-blocking each other.
"拆档"  你搞笑吧
"Crotch-blocking"? Really?
是我那个教北欧历史的老教授
It's my old nordic-history professor.
他办公室的人说他就快到了
His office says he's almost here.
小香草太太
Mrs. Vanilla.
我们找到你的钱包了
We found your wallet!
朗多  谢谢
Rondo, thank you!
你是在哪里找到的  朗多
Oh! Where'd you find it, Rondo?
我知道不会是你们拿的
I knew you guys didn't take it.
我们去翻了垃圾  丹尼亚在一个垃圾箱里找到的
Well, we checked the trash. Dania found it in a dumpster.
没丢东西吧  妈
Is everything there, ma?
我看看  驾照  银行卡  现金
Well, my license, my ATM card, my cash --
少了一百块
I'm missing 100 bucks.
你确定吗  小香草太太
Are you sure, Mrs. Vanilla?
好了  道格  走吧  我们去楼上备案
Okay, Dawg, let's go. We're going upstairs to booking.
不  简  等等  我来处理这事
No, Jane, wait. Let me handle this.
你妈妈会怎么想
How would your mother feel?
她不会很为你骄傲了吧
She wouldn't be very proud, would she?
道格没有母亲
Um... Dawg doesn't have a mother.
他母亲去世了
His mother passed.
我  我真抱歉
Oh, I'm -- I'm sor--
别哭
Don't cry.
坚强点  没事
Don't cry. All right.
不是他干的
He didn't do it.
他是在替我顶罪
He's covering for me.
钱我没用  我这就还给你
The money's there. I put it back.
丹尼亚  你为什么偷我的钱
Dania, why would you steal from me?
我需要一百块买课本
I needed $100 for a textbook.
那你怎么不跟老师说呢
Well, why didn't you tell the teacher?
我不想让她知道...
I didn't want her to know --
知道什么
What?
知道你住在青少年收容所
that -- that you live in a teen shelter?
对
Yeah.
你去了洗手间
You went to the bathroom.
我就从你包里拿走了钱包
I took the wallet out of your purse.
道格看到你回来
Dawg saw you coming,
就拉响了警报掩护我
and he pulled the alarm to cover for me.
我真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我也很抱歉
I'm sorry, too.
简
Jane.
这是波士顿剑桥大学
This is professor Walter Lowell
北欧研究学院的
from the Department of Scandinavian Studies
沃特・罗威尔教授
at Boston Cambridge University.
你好  很高兴见到你
Hello. It's nice to meet you.
这是我的荣幸
The pleasure is mine.
艾尔斯医生正要给我看些
Dr. Isles was about to show me some letters
你们想让我翻译的
written in the rune alphabet
古代北欧文写的书信
that you all would like me to translate.
对  信在这里
Yes. I have some of the letters here.
我们把原版复印过了
We made copies of the originals.
软盘
Oh, floppy disks?
我当然还记得
Oh, yes, I certainly do remember
软盘是原版的那个年代
when the floppies were the originals.
之前你说"老"的时候  我真没想到
When you said "old," I didn't realize
你是指他曾跟奥拉夫一起当过海盗
that you meant he and Olaf went on Viking raids together.
他耳朵不好使  但他会读唇语
He's hard of hearing, but he can read lips.
这些看上去像是用原始诺尔斯语写的
These appear to be written in proto-norse.
那是种在北欧使用的印欧语
That's an Indo-European language spoken in Scandinavia.
人们认为它在
It's thought to have evolved
公元一世纪后发展成了一种原始的
as a Proto-Germanic Northern dialect
德国北部方言
over the 1st century A.D..
行行好  一个书呆子讲话就够了
Please -- one nerd at a time.
这些是情书
Well, these are love letters
写给一位名叫无骨奥拉夫的维京人
addressed to a viking by the name of Olaf the Boneless.
可那在  那在历史上是错的
No, that's -- that's historically incorrect.
应该是无骨伊娃
It's Ivar the Boneless.
希望他不是以小时收费的
I hope he's not charging us by the hour.
别说了
Stop.
这些信是奥拉夫的情人
They were written by Olaf's lover,
一个叫古娜希尔德的维京女人写的
a viking maiden by the name of Gunnhild.
我的天呐
Oh, dear.
奥拉夫还跟另一个叫温特玛特的维京女人
Olaf was still married to a different viking maiden
结了婚呢
by the name of Undirmaor.
知道吗  温特玛特的意思是...
You know, "undirmaor" means --
不是时候  莫拉
Not now, Maura.
他到底是有多迷这个游戏啊
Exactly how deep into this game was he?
听听这个
Listen to this.
"你天鹅绒般柔软的胡须仍在
"Your velvety beard still hums
我温软的胸脯上低吟"
against the bosom of my tender flesh."
好的  非常感谢你的帮助
Okay. Well, uh, you've been very helpful.
矛上发现的DNA跟
The DNA recovered from the spear is a match
死者身上找到的DNA吻合
for the DNA found on the victim.
是来自于同一个女人
It's from the same woman.
谢谢  苏西
Thank you, Susie.
这是重大突破
Okay, well, that's a big break.
是啊
Yep.
很高兴见到您
It was nice to meet you.
不  别走
Oh, no, no, no, no,
信我还没读完呢
I'm not finished with your letters.
坐
Sit. Sit.
喝点茶
Have some tea.
寒冷是女性的安抚
"Cold are the counsel of women."
的确很冷
Cold, indeed.
在受害人电脑上发现什么了吗
Find anything on the victim's computer?
没什么有用的  他只用电脑来玩网游
Nothing useful. He jus used it to play M.M.O.S
真搞不懂他的生意是怎么成功的
No idea how he had a successful business.
我猜和一群维京人玩游戏
I guess playing with geirlaug of gongu
比做啤酒有趣多了
is more fun than making beer.
维京王国游戏制作者
"Vikings of the realm" Game makers
发了一些用户信息
sent over subscriber information --
格雷格・扬森和12000人玩过
12,000 names of people Greg Jensen played with.
正当我准备逐个排查的时候  简的信息救了我
I was about to go through them when Jane rescued me.
她人你
Where is she?
被唠叨的教授困住了
Trapped with professor windbag.
温特玛特和古娜希尔德
Undirmaor and...gunnhild?
没找到那个女孩  但我找到了这个
I can't find under-girl, but I found the other one.
古娜希尔德真是性感
Gunnhild is va-va-va-voom!
真名是肯德拉・迪
Her name is Kendra Dee.
她在南边的家里登陆
She logs in from her house in south end --
恰巧坐落在里总局不远的地方
Conveniently located just minutes from us.
我现在很闲  我能帮你去接她
I'm not doing anything. I could help you pick her up.
是的  这就是我的化身
Yes, that's my avatar.
看不出来吗
Can't you tell?
能  的确很像
Yeah. Quite the resemblance.
你和格雷格・扬森有外遇吗
Were you having an affair with Greg Jensen?
有过
Oh,was.
这是我一生中最激情的外遇
It was the most intensely passionate affair of my life.
我们在萨尼特岛上做爱
We made love on the isle of thanet,
还有诺丁汉  约克
Nottingham, york.
女士  这是在IRL中吗
Ma'am, was this I.R.L.?
很迷人  很魔幻
It was enchanting and magical.
奥拉夫为我倾倒
Olaf swept me off my feet.
我问的不是这个
That's not what I asked.
是在IRL中吗
Was it I.R.L.?
不是
It was not.
IRL是啥
What's "I.R.L."?
现实世界
"In real life."
女士  见过这个吗
Ma'am, have you seen this before?
没见过  但我会读符文
No, but I can read rune letters.
这是我爱人的名字
It's the name of my lover --
无骨奥拉夫
"Olaf the boneless."
这些信是你写给格雷格・扬森的吗
Did you write these letters to Greg Jensen?
是写给奥拉夫
To olaf.
他死了真可惜
It's a shame he's dead.
肯定是温特玛特干的
This has to be the work of undirmaor.
她竭尽所能要分开我们
She did everything in her power to drive us apart.
你知道在IRL中
Do you know who undirmaor is in the, uh...
温特玛特是谁吗
the I.R.L.?
不知道
No. I do not.
但记住我的话  我会找到她的
But mark my words -- I will get that woman.
拿着我的名片  在你下手之前打给我
Take my card a-and call me before you do that.
女士
Ma'am.
格雷格・扬森在IRL被杀了
Greg Jensen was killed I.R.L.
是  被一个RP
Yeah. By an R.P.
也就是真人
"Real person."
是简
It's Jane.
我们需要擦拭一下你的唾液来获取DNA样本
We'd like to do a cheek swab for a dna sample.
如果是必要的话
If you must.
该死
Darn!
现在我要跟谁玩啊
Who am I gonna play with now?
老天啊
Oh, my god.
我以为那个教授
I thought that professor
说内裤再也说不完了
would never stop talking about underwear.
温特玛特黑客技术不错
Undirmaor has got mad hacking skills.
不断变化账号  删除历史
Keeps changing accounts, deleted her avatar's history.
这是谁啊  是古娜希尔德
Well, what do you know? It's gunnhild.
很可爱
She's cute.
1963年以后她就不长这样了
She stopped looking like that in 1963.
她在一个秘密的游戏活动中
She's at a secret gaming event.
我被邀请了
I'm invited.
DNA结果还没出来
Well, the dna results haven't come back yet.
她可能是凶手
She could be our killer.
她说她准备和温特玛特联系
She's says she's about to make contact with undirmaor.
做吧
Let's go.
那是波吉尔
There's porgeir.
这是索
And there's thor.
还有格雷迪
And grettir.
和雷弗
And refur!
雷弗
"Refur"?
我没有看到她
Well, I don't see my date.
说出你的喜好  维京人
Speak your preference, viking kin --
袭击  打劫  掠夺  屠杀
Raiding, looting, pillaging, slaughtering.
或许  血斧埃里克见过她
Maybe...Erich the blood ax has seen her.
你的名字  小妞
Whoa! Your name, wench?
里佐利警探  波士顿凶案组
Detective Rizzoli, Boston homicide.
抱歉  我们在角色扮演
I'm sorry. W-we're role-playing.
看出来了
Get it, yeah.
我们在找一个叫古娜希尔德的维京人
Uh, we're looking for a viking named "Gunnhild."
当然  那个宝贝
Sure, yeah -- the babe.
她在下面的区域
She's in the lower realm.
你只剩一条命了
Come on! You've only got one life left.
我要从头开始
And I got to go back to the beginning.
糟了
Oh, crap.
迪小姐  肯德拉
Mrs. D! Kendra!
请求支援  我们要封锁这里
Call for backup. We got to lock this place down.
你 说你呢
Hey, you. You! Hey!
我需要索利漫画店区域的所有单位来支援
I need all units in the area at solly's comic store.
你看见有人进去过吗
Did you see anyone come in here?
没有  先生  是女士  女士
Uh, no, sir. Ma'am. Ma'am.
要确保任何人都不能出去  可以吗
Make sure nobody leaves this store, all right?
快去
Go on!
她被短剑刺死
She was stabbed with a dagger --
和游戏里一样
Just like in the game.
温特玛特到底是谁
Who the hell is undirmaor?
她就是凶手
Because that's our killer.
说你有线索
Tell me you have something
因为没找到目击者
'cause we don't have a single witness.,
我在肯德拉的外衣上找到一丝头发  没有发根
Well, I found a hair on Kendra's cloak. No root ball.
但是我们在用一种新的法医激光技术
But we are trying a new forensic laser technique.
运用紫外线和质谱分析法
It uses ultraviolet light and mass spectrometry.
请快进
Faster, please.
击中头发  把它变成气体
Zaps the hair and turns it into a gas.
这和两起凶案又有什么联系
Explain how that's gonna help me solve two murders.
它可以查明凶手在过去一年里
It may help us determine what the killer ate and drank
都吃喝了什么
over the last year.
知道凶手吃了什么怎么就有帮助了呢
How is knowing how many ding dongs our suspect ate helpful?
头发质谱分析法的结果出来了
The mass spectrometer results are back on the hair tests.
我知道你在等
I know you've been waiting for them.
谢谢
Thank you.
因为头发长得很慢
Because hair grows slowly over time,
它会建立一种时间线
It creates a timeline of sorts.
好吧
Okay.
那凶手在四月的早餐
So, what did the killer eat --
我看看
Uh, let me see --
都吃了什么
for breakfast in April?
有意思
That's interesting.
的确
It certainly is.
草莓华夫饼  鸡蛋松饼
Strawberry waffles? Eggs benedict?
什么嘛
What?
发酵须鲸和羊头芝士
Fermented minke whale and sheep's head cheese.
假设一个人想要吃发酵须鲸
Where would you get minke whale
和羊头芝士的话
and sheep's head cheese,
要去哪里才能买得到
assuming you'd want it?
斯堪的纳维亚
Um...Scandinavia?
Scandinavia.
莫拉  "温特玛特"是什么意思
Maura, what does "Undirmaor" mean?
英语里吗
In English?
不是  是在霍比特语里
No. In Proto-hobbit.
当然是在英语里啦
Yes, in English!
下属或是学徒
"Underling" or "apprentice".
学徒
Apprentice.
或是助手
Or assistant.
莫拉  我们认识一个
Maura, we know someone
可能一直在吃鲸鱼或是羊的人
who's probably been eating whale or sheep.
拿到证明了  她的不在场证明纯属瞎编
Got a warrant. Alibi was bullshit.
航空公司刚刚证实了
The airline just confirmed.
罗比・伯克  格雷格・扬森的助理
Ruby Burke, Greg Jensen's assistant,
用剩余机票搭乘了早一班航班从雷克雅末克飞了回来
flew standby on an earlier flight from Reykjavik.
干得好  弗罗斯特
Nice, Frost.
好的  谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
罗比今天没去上班
Ruby didn't show up to work today.
她正在某处玩"维京王国"呢
She's playing "Vikings of the Realm" somewhere.
难不成我要在游戏里发通缉令吗
So I put a bolo out in the realm?
不用  我建了个游戏人物来找她
No. I built an avatar to find her.
长得跟你真像呀
Looks just like you.
我们得伪装一下嘛
We got to go in disguise.
我还是不明白这个白痴游戏有什么好玩的
I still don't understand the point of this stupid game.
有什么好难理解的
Well, what is so hard about it?
无非就是袭击几艘船  抢夺村庄
You raid ships, plunder villages,
杀几个敌兵就赢了
kill sworn enemies to win.
能赢来什么  虚拟情人吗
Win what? A fantasy lover?
等一下
Wait a minute.
我觉得这和输赢无关
I don't think this is about winning.
我认为动机是爱情
I think this is about love.
你认为格雷格・样色和罗比在现实中有外遇
You think Greg Jensen was having a real affair with Ruby?
我说不准  也许不算是外遇吧
I don't know. It wasn't much of an affair.
没有证据显示她曾出现在他的爱巢中
There wasn't any evidence of her at his love nest,
而且我们发现的分泌物和精液残留
and the secretions and the seminal fluid
也都有一个月之久了
that we found were a month old.
除非扬森是因为可怜她而跟她上床
Unless Jensen had pity sex.
可怜她
Pity sex?
是呀  就那么一次
Yeah, one-time pity sex,
然后他就把她扔去了斯堪的纳维亚
right before he sent Ruby to Scandinavia.
他冷淡了她
I mean, he froze her out --
不管是现实生活中还是在游戏中
in real life and in the game, too.
所以罗比肯定在游戏中跟踪他
So, Ruby must have stalked him in the game,
发现他找了个新的虚拟情人
figured out that he had a new virtual lover...
古娜希尔德也就是肯德拉・迪
"Gunnhild", a.k.a Kendra Dee.
弗罗斯特
Frost...
看看奥拉夫是否在线
check and see if Olaf is online.
奥拉夫  但是格雷格・扬森在现实中已经死了
Olaf? But Greg Jensen is dead in the I.R.L.
那你怎么解释奥拉夫仍在自己的爱巢中登陆游戏呢
So explain why Olaf is online in his Back Bay love nest.
不是奥拉夫  而是温特玛特
Not Olaf -- Undirmaor.
罗比  把手举起来
Ruby, put your hands in the air.
奥拉夫  我的挚爱
Olaf, my love.
温特玛特  你终于来了
Undirmaor. At last -- you're here.
罗
Ru --
她根本都不知道咱们的存在
She doesn't even know we're here.
科萨克  把那东西拔了
Korsak, unplug that thing.
不
No.
不  奥拉夫
No! Olaf!
奥拉夫  求求你  回来呀  我的挚爱
Olaf, please come back, my love.
罗比  一切都结束了
Ruby, it's over.
没有
It's not over.
我们终于在一起了
We were finally together.
开机呀
Turn it on.
把他带回来
Bring him back.
他回不来了
He's not coming back.
格雷格已经死了  罗比
Greg is dead, Ruby.
我爱他
I loved him.
他也爱我
He loved me.
他到底是爱罗比・伯克还是温特玛特呢
Did he love Ruby Burke, or did he love Undirmaor?
他爱我
He loved me.
我
Me.
奥拉夫爱温特玛特  我以为
Olaf loved Undirmaor, and I thought...
天啊  如果他要是知道温特玛特就是我的话
Oh, God, if only, if only he knew that it was me --
就是我  就是罗比  一直在他身边
Me, Ruby, right there all along...
你向他表明身份到底是在你们一个月前上床之前
Did you tell him who you were before or after
还是在那之后
you slept with him a month ago?
我把我的身体献给了他
I gave him my flesh.
可当我告诉他我就是温特玛特的时候  他
And when I told him I was Undirmaor, he just...
他把我派走了
He sent me away.
罗比  你因谋杀格雷格・扬森而被捕了
Ruby, you're under arrest for the murder of Greg Jensen.
不  不  求求你们把游戏打开吧
No! No! Please turn it back on!
还有谋杀肯德拉・迪
And Kendra Dee.
不  不  他没有死
No! No, he's not gone!
不  他没有死
No, he's not gone!
不会的
He can't be!
他不会死的
He can't be gone!
蹲监狱
Aah! Go right to jail!
到我了  我要买地产
My turn. I want to buy me some property.
希望你把你的上好餐具都藏起来了
Hope you hid the good silver.
你装得一副冷酷的样子
You pretend to be such a badass,
但你实际上很心软
but you're really a pushover.
我很开心你邀请了他们过来
I'm glad you brought them here.
怎么着  方便你研究异常青春期行为
Why? So you could study aberrant juvenile behavior?
他们只是需要别人的注意和一点点支持
They just need some attention, a little support.
他们从来都没玩过桌游
I mean, they've never played a board game.
太难以置信了
Can you believe that?
就是啊
I know.
莫拉  你在这面包里放了多少大蒜呀
Maura, how much garlic did you put on this bread?
-六瓣  -六
- Six cloves. - Six cl--
他们是无家可归的孩子而已  又不是吸血鬼
They're homeless teenagers. They're not vampires.
丹尼亚怎么办
What about Dania?
我会盯着她的
Well, I'm gonna keep an eye on her.
你也是
and so were you.
我们会确保她把她的聪明才智用到正事上
We'll make sure she puts that big brain to good use.
我和卡瓦诺夫谈了
I talked to Cavanaugh.
导师项目成为正式的了
The mentor program is now official.
我想要停车的地方
I wanted park place!
不好意思了  小香草太太
Oh, too bad,, Mrs. Vanilla.
-小香草  -干吗
- Hey Vanilla. - Yeah.
我是地主了
I'm a landlord.
从没想过我会邀请朗多来家里玩
I never pictured an evening in with Rondo.
简
Jane
你觉得你母亲她不会
You don't think your mum might...
我不想看起来很无情  但是
I don't want to seem uncharitable, but...
放心  我会确保朗多的次品家人
Yeah. I'll make sure that Rondo's reject family
不会搬进你家客房
doesn't move into your guest house.
谁饿了
Who's hungry?
我饿死了
I'm starving.
我也是
Me too.
-看起来很美味呀  -小心烫
- Man, this looks good! -It's hot.
不  不  不  看着  这样就好了
No, no, no. Just look, like this.
好吧
Okay.
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：free 浮世闲生 janice 陈小圈 喜乐 小蛮腰 zeez
校对：zeez   时间轴：贝壳 密斯恩
后期：随风飞翔      总监   zeez
妙女神探  第三季第十三集
&神探
妙女&
第十三集
第三季
■